habanaija.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Haba Naija! Forums Lifestyle Culture & More....

Haba Naija Privacy Statement

## Privacy Policy for www.HabaNaija.com

Effective Date: 21st November 2012

At Haba Naija we are committed to protecting your privacy whenever you are on our website or communicate with us via email.

Our Privacy Policy is contained below and provides a detailed explanation as to how we may use your personal information.

**Information We Collect from You**  
If you register for information by filling out a form we can collect the information provided.

Traffic data, weblogs, location data, and any other communication are collected. These details come from your visit to our site and any resource tools you use while on the site, this information is not linked to you personally, this is just general information collected to let us know traffic coming to our site.

**Use of Cookies**  
Circumstances may arise when we may need to gather information about your computer to help provide appropriate services to you. The data gathered is solely to enhance your user experience of our site and not for any other reason.

No identifying information will be shared about our visitors and how they made use of our site. No personal details will ever be shared.

Any computer has the option to decline cookies. Your web browser options include an “enable” button to decline cookies. It is imperative that you understand by declining cookies you may be limiting your access to sections of our website.

**Use of Your Information**  
Information collected and stored is used solely to make your user experience easier and faster at your next visit to Haba Naija. We do not share or sell your information to third parties.

**Storing Your Personal Data**  
Outside of the European Economic Area are places for storing and processing data we collect from you. We may take advantage of these outside areas, allowing an employee to process data collected from you. These processors may work for our suppliers. The transfer of this data may include processing and completing your order on our site, such as utilising your payment information or offering support services.

We take all reasonable care to ensure your data is secure and in agreement with our Privacy Policy as outlined here.

Secured servers are used by our company to ensure proper data storage. Information on transactions is kept encrypted for safety measures.

Transmission of data on the Internet can never be ultimately secure. We do not and cannot guarantee security of information collected electronically or transmitted; however, we take all necessary steps to provide the best security available.

As a result of our inability to guarantee safety, you are submitting information to us at your own risk. Where needed a password may be necessary to access areas of our site. You are responsible for the safety and confidentiality of the password you generate.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or any services from Haba Naija, please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://www.habanaija.com/contact-us/ "contact us").
